Ladies and gentlemen welcome
女士们先生们 你们好
My name is Walker Stipe with palo alto education
我是来自Palo Alto Education的Walker Stipe
and today o today to date today
今天，没错就是今天
We have a special treat
我们有特别惊喜
Perhaps you have read or watched
你以前可能读过 或者看过
any portion of the harry potter series
哈利波特系列的其中任意一部分
if you haven't my soul cries out for that sadness
如果你没看过 那真是太可惜了
it is so good it get on it
特别好看而且一直都很棒
this world is a magical world
书中的世界是个魔法世界
this school we see here is Hogwarts
图片上这个学校是霍格沃茨魔法学校
oh my gosh Hogwarts is gorgeous
天啊噜 这个学校棒呆了
Now Hogwarts  is a school as we mentioned
我们提到了霍格沃茨是个学校
if you were to go to the school
如果你在这儿上学
you would be in one of the four classes that this school has
你肯定在四个学校其中一个就学
for instance you could be in Gryffindor
比如说你在格兰芬多
very proud and brave type of person
因为你自豪而勇敢
you could be a Hufflepuff
你可能在赫奇帕奇
very courageous and enduring
因为你勇猛有耐心
you could be a ravenclaw
你可能在拉文克劳
potentially a little bit quirky and brilliant
可能你古怪又聪明
last but not least is the silver and ambition is your aim
最后 你可能在斯莱特林 因为你野心勃勃
and nothing will get in your way
没什么能阻挡你
now to determine which of these houses you will be put into
如果要决定你要去哪个学院
there is no teacher
可没有哪个老师
or professor and no magician shall
教授或者魔法师
take upon themselves this task no no
能完成这项艰难的任务
have a hat you betcha
我们有分院帽 你猜对了
that's what we are making today we're making a hat
我们今天就是要做一顶帽子
welcome to walker stipes haberdashery
欢迎来到walker stipe的杂货铺
where we're gonna make a hat
我们要在这做个帽子
now this hat is a magical hat
这是一定魔法帽子
whoa magic hats don't mind if I do
哇 魔法帽子诶
and this hat can can tell who you are
这帽子能告诉你你是谁
and tell a lot about you and
你的各种信息
can determine okay this this person has
这个人有很多
of the attributes that I associate with
帽子熟悉的格兰芬多特质
a Gryffindor this guy he's a Gryffindor
所以这个人该去格兰芬多
same house as Harry Potter Hermione and Ronald Weasley themselves
和哈利 赫敏 罗恩一个学院
or perhaps like wow this guy he's a shoot for star
或者这是一个追求卓越的人
like puffett and slyterin and he's one of those guys
比如普菲特和斯莱特林 他是他们中的一员
so we don't have magic
但是我们没有魔法
oh wait yes yes we do yes yes yes yes
等等 我们有啊
yes we do we have machine learning Wow
我们有机器学习呀
machine learning ladies and gentlemen is going bethe magic we use to create our hat
他将会施展魔法为我们造一顶帽子
this hat will enable us to not of course read the minds up
他当然不会教我们读心术
we will bypass that part by merely asking questions
帽子只会问一些问题
and then with those answers that will be what we know about the
有了这些答案 我们就知道
new student at Hogwarts which today is you
霍格沃茨新生 也就是你的信息啦
so welcome to Hogwarts
欢迎来到霍格沃茨
we're gonna make your own magical hat
我们要自己做分院帽咯
let's hop in
让我们开始吧
already we're jumping in first thing you
我们进网站了 首先
want to do you is want to go to machinelearningforkids. com
登陆machinelearningforkids.com
the particular URL you're looking for is this one
你要输入的网址就是这个
but a quick google search of machinelearningforkids should do the trick
google直接搜索也行
so once you are here you want to go to worksheets
进来之后 点击工作表(worksheet)
you go to worksheets and you should hopefully see things look kind of like this
然后你可能会看到这些
what we're doing today is we're doing the sorting hat
我么今天要做的是分院帽
so click on this little guy here
点击这个蓝色按钮
and snag yourself this one this is the dude you want
选择第二个按钮 这是你要做的
what he looks like is this
他看起来怎么样
he looks like this well what a beautiful guy
就是这样 真是漂亮的家伙
this is what we're gonna be working through
我们今天就要在这里做帽子
we've done the conceptual side of getting ourselves ready
我们做好一些概念性的准备工作之后
now what we want to do is we want to get started
然后我们就正式开始啦
so want to go to your projects
进入项目（projects)
make sure you're logged in
确保你已经登陆
this is important otherwise you're you can't save anything
这很重要 不然你什么都保存不了了
so make sure logged in
所以再次确保你已登陆
once you go to projects
点进项目之后
to make a new project
选择创造一个新项目（add a new project）
name it sorting hat or something like that you'll remember
把它命名为分院帽或者你类似的你记得的名字
then what we're doing is we want to Train it
然后我们就要训练它啦 点击训练（train）
by training we need to have some sort of data to train on of course
当然啦 训练的话我们得需要数据
so what data are we training on
所以我们需要怎样的数据呢
well first we need to get our classes
首先我们得有学院的数据
we have our Gryffindor Hufflepuff Slytherin and our ravenclaw houses
我们有格兰芬多 赫奇帕奇 斯莱特林和拉文克劳学院
we need to fill each of these houses
所以我们要给这些学院
with things that are well suited to these to these houses
加上一些符合该学院的信息
so what I did is I went on to the googles
所以我在谷歌上搜索了
and I looked up quotes from particular people who are part of these houses
不同学院不同人说的一些话
for instance for Gryffindor
比如说格兰芬多里
I chose Ronald Weasley because he is one of my favorite
我选择了罗恩 因为他是我最喜欢的角色
for Hufflepuff i chose Ceedric Diggory found some wonderful quotes by him
赫奇帕奇里我选了塞德里克 找到了一些很棒的话
Slytherin of course draco malfoy was my
go-to character and then for Ravenclaw
luna lovegood who is not so good so good
she's awesome
[Music]
alright so then we have we have those
and you do need a lot of them afraid to
say I did not try with just five of each
but I presume that you do need ten all
right once we have done so then then
then then we go back to project you may
be wondering Walker why did you move
over to the side well we're about to
find out as we move to the next stage
the next stage is where we create the
magic the magic is about to happen
ladies and gentlemen get excited what
we're gonna do is enter into the Hall of
elements by pressing you learn and test
button magical then we shall do the
sorcery the sorcery is enacted by waving
our wand very precipitously and then
clicking on this button here yes when we
do this it'll take some time the magic
takes time but once it is complete then
we have a magical hat
the reason I'm over to the side is so
that I don't block the button that is
the magic behind that
so let us enact the magic alrighty this
hopefully is what we see on our screen
now or something very similar to it
because this tells us that the magic
that we have conjured up has done
something something's happened now let's
say we're trying to turn a cat into a
dog a cat into a cup a lamp a house
whatever maybe a dragon okay we're just
trying to turn it into something in this
instance we're trying to turn our
computer into a hat of course that's
that's what we're trying to do now this
doesn't mean that it actually turned it
into a hat that works so let's let's
test it let's see if this this guy works
I hope I hope that analogy made some
sense we're gonna check if this works
that's what we're doing now alright so
we're gonna go back we're gonna go into
scratch we're gonna open it in scratch
we're gonna open it and scratch their
scratch and here is the portion where
you get to have a little bit of fun a
little bit of more funds for our having
a great time to make some artwork yeah
get to make some fancy pantsy hats so
you can stick with the wizard hat if
you'd like you don't have to give it a
face you can you can also do a top hat
you could do a fedora you could do a
gown it's not a gown a tiara that's what
it's called thinking like Cinderella
stuff and even one of those hats with
the cool little pinwheels on top they're
like the propellers do it's a thing I
don't know what's called the cool
after you do this you're going to create
the script oh the script is script
descriptive yes yes yes
it's gonna look like this these are they
gonna be the general framework of it
make sure you change the the text that
it will say do something reasonable once
you have done so you will arrive at
something you're making fun of my
artwork right now aren't you you're
making fun of that well guess what me
and my mom both think it's amazing so
it's amazing there it is I'm a great
artist and there's that all right we
have our script we have our our model is
implemented here it's all this stuff
right here we're ready we're ready to
see if our magic has created a good hat
let's see how well our hat works
let us try some exact exact of Mundo
quotes from the draco malfoy himself
yeah so one of the things that draco
malfoy said was honestly if you were any
slower you'd be going backwards what a
charmer what a nice guy so this is a
data point that we trained them this is
the exact word egde that the model
learned so if it doesn't give a slither
and something is horribly awry and we
may be doing pyromancy when we thought
we were a frost mage so let's find out I
know about you but I was nervous what
this means is that at the very minimum
our hat has learned to memorize yes all
right let's look at some
other things that Ronald Weasley has
spoken so one of the things he said is
don't let the muggles get you down for
anyone who doesn't know muggles are you
and me the people without magical powers
now we are gaining our magical powers
through the power of machine learning so
very soon we're gonna get our message in
the mail from the owls to hop on
Hogwarts and it will be awesome where we
learn to be full-fledged wizards
handedly amazing so here it worked it
actually worked
now we're going to try something a
little bit ambitious in fact so
ambitious that is the word that we're
going to use because chem vicious is
associated with the house of Slytherin
ambition at all costs so let's see if it
learned it it didn't it didn't learn it
what I want all this work I'm using the
magic of machine learning in here it
doesn't even learn that Slytherin is
ambitious
it's a bad hat yeah actually you're
right
you're not even ruffled you're correct
it's not a great hat okay
it's learned let's learn to memorize
okay it's learned a little bit about
Ronald Weasley it's learned a little bit
about Draco Malfoy look at that face but
it's not learned Slytherin
it is not learned Gryffindor and all
that that means if you watch those
movies if read those books but you like
get that so well so how did we get our
hat to be even better one of the things
you will hear more and more if you are
in the realm of data science at all
is more data you need more data you know
you need to see more of the you know
more about Harry Potter and more about
Hermione and all these famous Gryffindor
characters and then eventually you may
realize like okay I'm understanding the
essence of what it means to be a
Gryffindor or whatever so with our small
10 samples we've really learned because
what we trained on particularly was
quotes by Draco so we're gonna learn
Draco pretty well but he's not all of
Slytherin we've learned Ronald Weasley
pretty well but not necess
all of Gryffindor because I guess kind
of cheated if you want to say it like
that but that's what we have done and as
we see it works well for what we trained
on but if we look for things that we
have not trained on we probably need
more data to get a better vision of the
magical world all righty
we've made it ladies and gentlemen
welcome welcome to Hogwarts where we
learn with Sheena learning all day long
and become better wizards and more
friendly people all the day long we done
today what have we done well we created
a hat what does this hat do wonderful
question this hat is a classifier hat
all right so we have four classes right
we have our Gryffindor's we have our
slytherins and we have a hufflepuffs and
what we want to do is we want to tell is
this person just does he fit in here
does he is easy as leather is this ass
leather in person this is a is this a
ravenclaw see so Hufflepuff or perhaps a
Gryffindor now as we see it wasn't it
wasn't it wasn't easy okay it learns
some things but it didn't learn all
things and maybe your model when you
test it you know it does actually well
or it doesn't do very well on on certain
things and there many things we can do
to get that better but even the best
Wizards in the land I'm talking I'm
talking Godric Gryffindor I'm talking
I'm talking Harry Potter himself a
Dumbledore perhaps even dare I say it's
Voldemort that's right I said it
I did it they even have a hard time with
this okay these are very very difficult
spells to master natural language
processing is the type of magic that
this is this is not pyromancy we're not
being a frost mage or even a necromancer
okay this is known as natural language
processing because language it's natural
it's what we speak talking about wizards
and whatever and we want to you know
process this information we won't want
to know stuff about what we're saying
that's literally what that means is
knowing what the heck we're talking
about so it's really really hard and
even Dumbledore has a hard time so what
this means is that there's a ton of
research being done to this there are
great minds great Wizards doing
incredible things all over the globe to
attempt to get better at understanding
words so as we can see with our half
that we made here we can do some things
but it's still very hard so I hope we
have
sited some excitement towards the magic
of this great new realm known as natural
language processing also known as words
so once again this is Walker Stipe from
Palo Alto education hoping that you have
a wonderful wonderful day thank you and
goodbye